Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-104
  - Articles: Computer: General 6/2/1980 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Articles: Database Management Systems 8/19/1980 - 3/22/1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Articles: Distributed Computing 5/16/1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Articles: Higher Education 1970 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Articles: Information 1980 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Articles: Forecasting 6/16/1980 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Articles: Libraries 9/9/1980 - 3/12/1981 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Articles: Management 11/13/1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Donald Kennedy – Edward E. Shaw Correspondence 6/6/1980 -6/2/1981 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Legal: Patricia Palmer Appeal 3/17/1978 - 5/31/1980 confidential (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Legal: Patricia Martinez Grievance 11/12/1977 - 7/15/1983 confidential (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Legal: Bing Nursery 5/10/1974 - 12/10/1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Legal: SLAC Chronological File 3/19/69 - 4/24/1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Legal: Boole and Babbage Background Material 6/6/1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Legal: Corporate Articles and Bylaws 3/7/1977 - 3/8/1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Legal: Copyright Agreements - 1977 7/13/1977 - 1/12/1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Legal: Copyright 12/19/1977 - 4/8/1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Legal: General 3/5/1971 - 11/30/1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Legal: Copyright 1/2/1975 - 3/26/1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Legal: Legislation 6/4/1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Legal: Patent 6/10/1970 - 5/5/1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Legal: Personnel 12/4/1974 - 12/5/1979 confidential (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Legal: Mentel, Inc. Litigation 10/31/1978 - 10/27/1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Legal: Pacific Telephone 6/6/1968 - 1/20/1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Legal: Privacy 10/26/1972 - 10/17/1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Legal: SCIP User Cases 2/2/1977 - 4/25/1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Legal: Software 3/25/1981 - 3/29/1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Legal: 1977 Taxes 1/21/1976 -2/1/1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Legal: Sales Tax 10/24/1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Legal: Trademark 2/19/1977 - 6/16/1980 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Libraries: Academic Council Committee on Libraries 5/23/1975 - 12/21/1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Libraries: Academic Staff: Libraries 10/29/1977 - 10/19/1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Libraries: Academic Council Committee on Libraries 3/30/1977 - 10/24/1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Libraries: “The Future of Library Automation at Stanford” Weber 9/1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Libraries: Budget 5/25/1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Libraries: University of California 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Libraries: Organizational Models 11/1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Libraries: Ad Hoc Committee on Library Organization Report 3/1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Libraries: Compensation Proposal 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Libraries: SUL Annual Report 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Libraries: SUL Annual Report 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Libraries: “The Next Fifty Years” Weber 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Libraries: Library Bulletins 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Libraries: UC Berkeley - Stanford Research Library Program 10/11/1975 - 2/10/1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Libraries: General Computer Science, Chemistry, German, etc. 3/26/1973 - 5/14/1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Libraries: Greg Mills Visit & Study 11/1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Libraries: University Library, General 7/6/1976 - 10/7/1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Libraries: Main Library User Privileges, External and Internal 10/4/1976 - 12/22/1976 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Libraries: Pennsylvania State University Academic Staff Librarians 12/14/1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Libraries: Harvard University Study on Compensation 1/1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Libraries: Harvard Studies 9/1975 - 7/7/1977 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Libraries: “Library Management in the 1970’s” ARL 9/19/1977 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Libraries: Pittsburgh Study 12/6/1977 - 12/15/1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Libraries: Task Force on Library Planning 5/66 - 2/15/1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Libraries: Sub Task Force on Libraries 3/7/1979 -4/17/1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Libraries: Status of Librarians 1976-1977 8/26/1975 - 8/15/1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Libraries: Seven Springs Group 3/21/1977 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Articles: Miscellaneous 4/1978 - 11/1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Licensing: SPIRES 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Licensing: SPIRES 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Licensing: General 3/27/1970 - 12/6/1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Licensing: WYLBUR 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Licensing: WYLBUR 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Licensing: WYLBUR 1970 - 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - LOTS 9/29/1976 - 1/20/1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - MAG (Management Advisory Group) 11/19/1980 - 2/4/1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - MDP 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - MDP: CR-A OP 4/20/1979 - 5/7/1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - MDP 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - MDP Lecture 3/12/1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - MDP: Adjunct Activity 3/17/1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - MDP 1/8/1980 - 9/17/1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - CIT: Management Team 11/23/1981 - 4/15/1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mailnet 2/17/1982 - 3/1/1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Memoranda, General 9/17/1980 - 11/17/1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Practice Plan 12/4/1979 - 9/5/1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Systems Computer Applications Development 12/11/1979 - 3/18/1980 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Directors' Retreats Minutes 8/4/1973 - 9/26/1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Network Facilities 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Planning Retreat Reports 10/6/1973 - 5/21/1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - National Information Policy Teleconference 3/30/1981 - 1/28/1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research 5/19/1981 - 2/18/1982 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Network Division: Procurement RFP and Response 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Networks 6/5/1980 - 4/1/1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Networks: EDUNET 7/27/1978 - 5/8/1981 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Networks: SUNet 7/2/1982 - 8/31/1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Networks: EDUNET Fall 1977 - 4/21/1980 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Networks: CATV Report 3/11/1982 - 6/1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Networks: SUNet 6/17/1981 - 5/31/1983 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Electronics Communications Media Project 5/15/1982 - 8/25/1983 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Stanford University Strategy on Voice, Data, Video 11/4/1981 - 3/5/1982 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Names and Naming Conventions 10/5/1980 - 3/29/1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Networks: Proposal 7/1/1971 - 3/15/1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - SCIP Articles 5/18/1978 - 7/10/1979 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Non-disclosure Agreements: BNR, Inc. 10/10/1979 - 3/12/1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Non-disclosure Agreements: Associated Computer Consultant 2/6/1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Non-disclosure Agreements: Xerox Forms 11/15/1979 - 1/18/1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Disclosure Agreement Form (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - LOTS 4/13/1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Management (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Charts: Stanford University Basic Technologies (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Charts: CIT Management (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Charts: Administrative Information Systems Division (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Organizational Charts: Networking Development Division (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Charts: Instruction and Research, Information Systems Division (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Organizational Charts: Computer Systems and Services Division (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Organizational Charts: RLG Governance and Committee Structure (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Organizational Charts: RLG Central Organization (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Organization: CIT Medical Computing 3/5/1981 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Organization: BALLOTS/RLG/RLIN 2/14/1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Organization: CIT Memoranda 1/2/1980 - 6/26/1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Organization: Business Services - Accounting Information & Documentation Services Office 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - EARF (Electronic Application Research Forum) 5/21/1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Organization: SCIP 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Organization: SCIP 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Organization: University 1/4/1972 - 9/18/1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Performance/Utilization 3081 12/1981 - 1/5/1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Orvyl 11/18/1981 - 5/7/1982 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Organization and Management Study Group 12/7/1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Operating and Finance Group 10/3/1981 - 2/12/1982 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Office Information Systems 12/8/1981 - 7/29/1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Personnel: Stanford University Who's Who 10/1977 - 10/1978 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Personnel: RLIN Human Resources 7/10/1980 - 10/22/1980 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Personnel 8/19/1980 - 12/6/1982 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Personnel: Staff Development Program 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Personnel: Directory 3/7/1980 - 5/20/1981 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Personnel: Personnel Information System EDSHAW 10/27/1977 - 6/2/1978 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Personnel: ITS memos 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Press 10/3/1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Planning: Projects and Summary 7/17/1981 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Planning: Working File 5/22/1985 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Planning, Long Range 2/18/1981 - 7/16/1981 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Planning, Long Range: Personal Computers 9/11/1981 - 9/20/1981 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Planning, Long Range 10/4/1974 - 7/17/1975 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Planning, Long Range: 168 Installation Feasibility Team 2/20/1975 - 2/5/1976 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Planning, Long Range 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Planning, Short Range: CIT 12/28/1979 -3/5/1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Planning, Long Range: Stanford Land Use Plan 1980 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Planning, Long Range: General 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Planning, Long Range: SCIP Goals and Objectives 3/24/1973 - 3/24/1976 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Planning, Long Range: SLAC 5 Year Plan 1/1971 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Planning, Long Range: SLAC 4/27/1976 - 5/16/1978 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Planning, Long Range: Systems 3/15/1977 - 4/14/1977 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Planning, Long Range: Technical 12/9/1970 - 12/2/1980 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Planning, Long Range: General 1974-1979 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Planning, Long Range: Campus Facility 10/1976 - 7/1/1978 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Policy: CIT 9/2/1980 - 6/30/1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Policy: University 5/6/69 -5/5/1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Procurement, Equipment 12/1/1978 - 6/30/1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Procurement, Equipment: ADM 3 terminals 11/19/1976 - 12/27/1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Digital Equipment 5/28/1981 - 6/8/1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Amdahl 4/15/1977 - 7/23/1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Addressograph- Multigraph Acquisition 5/9/1978 - 10/30/1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Procurement, Equipment: ATD 11/19/1981 - 12/1/1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Ampex 8/10/1971 - 9/4/1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Procurement, Equipment: CDC 7/28/1971 - 4/19/1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Canon printer 4/11/1980 - 4/8/1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Centrex/Telecommunications 3/9/1978 - 4/25/1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Computers 3/14/1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Procurement, Equipment: CompuScan 4/16/1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Copiers and Reproduction Equipment 6/15/1976 - 9/6/1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Procurement, Equipment: DEC 5/5/1978 - 1/22/1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Procurement, Equipment: DEC Agreement 10/27/1971 - 8/1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Procurement, Equipment: DEC, General 10/23/67 - 8/4/1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Dataprint 11/5/1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Documentation 12/13/1979 - 3/21/1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Execuport Terminals 3/24/1980 - 4/2/1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Procurement, Equipment: DO Rating 10/1/1980 - 7/10/1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Procurement, Equipment: EM & M 6/5/1972 - 5/25/1975 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Procurement, Equipment 1970-1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Procurement, Equipment: General 1976-1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Procurement, Equipment: SLAC IBM Purchase Agreement 5/31/67 - 6/13/67 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Recommendation of IBM to AEC for SLAC 1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM Pricing and Contract Notices 1/20/1972 - 8/10/1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM Product Announcements 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM 3033 1/24/1979 - 3/10/1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM 3800 Printer 6/27/1977 - 4/17/1979 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM 4300 10/1/1979 - 9/28/1981 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM 370/168 3/28/1975 - 10/16/1975 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM, 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM Backlog Report 1/1/1970 - 4/29/1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Gandale 12/14/1979 -5/16/1980 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Hewlett Packard 8/3/1979 - 11/5/1980 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Telephone Company 4/7/1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Versatex Acquisition 10/10/1977 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Intel 9/21/1981 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Intel 3/16/1978 - 12/29/1980 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Mass Storage CALCOMP ATL 3/15/1978 - 4/6/1980 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Mass Storage ALT CALCOMP 12/8/1977 - 1/3/1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Memorex 11/12/1970 - 1/22/1980 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Multiplexor Channel Interface CHIF 3/23/1978 - 6/28/1978 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Procurement, Equipment: OCR 6/28/1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Prentice 12/9/1970 - 12/20/1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Printers 6/3/1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Procurement, Equipment: RFPs 168/3033N 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Procurement, Equipment: RCA Proposal 4/6/1961 - 4/20/1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Sanders 5/24/1971 - 1/24/1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Procurement, Equipment: STC 3/21/1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Terminals 4/23/1971 - 6/26/1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Tran 2/5/1975 - 5/16/1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Tymshare Corporation 3/12/1975 - 8/29/1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Xerox 12/19/1973 - 12/23/1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Com 12/20/1977 - 3/5/1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Computer Selection 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Data Entry Services 1/3/1974 - 12/20/1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Disks 6/27/1972 - 3/12/1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Procurement Evaluation: General 8/67 - 12/12/1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Micros 6/16/1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Procurement: Other Departments 3/24/67 - 8/24/1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Procurement, Software: Commissary 1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Procurement, Software: Amdahl Hyperviser 2/14/1978 - 6/13/1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Procurement, Software: APL 7/1/1975 - 10/8/1979 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Procurement, Software: ASM2 10/27/1977 - 2/19/1981 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Procurement, Software: ASSIST/RESOLVE 1/2/1976 - 9/22/1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Typewriters 11/29/1977 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Wang 4/30/1979 - 9/8/1982 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Procurement, Equipment: Technicon Data Systems Corporation Information 7/9/1982 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Procurement, Software: General, from 1976 2/12/1976 - 10/30/1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Procurement, Software: Mark IV Informatics 2/7/1975 - 8/28/1980 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Procurement, Software: OMSI-Pascal 8/22/1980 - 12/10/1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Procurement, Software: OSSIM 10/28/1977 -2/1/1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Procurement, Software Licenses: Pascal 1/7/1979 - 8/12/1981 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Procurement, Software Licenses: PAC II International Systems, Inc 8/20/1979 - 9/5/1979 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Procurement, Software: Personnel System 12/30/1977 - 7/18/1978 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Procurement, Software: IBM Program Products 11/15/1978 - 10/31/1979 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Procurement, Software: Patient Accounting System 3/30/1979 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Procurement, Software: Quasar 9/22/1982 - 10/6/1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Procurement, Software: PL/C 12/8/1970 - 11/5/1981 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Procurement, Software: Rand Information System 1401 6/10/1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Procurement, Software: SAS 3/18/1974 - 5/4/1983 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Procurement, Software: License, Waterloo 8/14/1981 - 8/21/1981 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Procurement, Software: Syncsort 5/27/1976 - 5/30/1981 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Procurement, Software: Script 8/24/1979 - 5/31/1981 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Procurement, Software: SPSS 4/2/1973 - 2/1/1980 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Procurement, Software: Reliability Plus 9/2/1977 - 4/5/1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, PLUS and IBM IREP 1 7/11/1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Procurement, Software: R/S Loader 8/20/1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Procurement, Software: Safeguard 2/7/1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Procurement, Software: SAPLOT/SAPMIN 5/5/1978 - 5/11/1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Procurement, Software: License, Surface II 10/28/1976 - 2/1/1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Procurement, Software: License, Tektronix Agreement 10/2/1979 - 10/11/1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Procurement, Software: TLMS 7/11/1974 - 7/10/1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Procurement, Software: Unilogic 4/24/1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Procurement, Software: UNIX 2/3/1982 - 11/17/1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Procurement, Software: UNIX Western Electric 8/15/1974 - 12/23/1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Procurement, Software: WATFIV 2/20/1975 - 8/5/1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Procurement, Software: Watsoft 5/11/1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, Rational/ Software, CMS Loader 1/1/1978 - 10/12/1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Procurement, Software: Waterloo CMS/WYLBUR 1/30/1978 - 7/20/1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Procurement Evaluation: HEG 8/13/1973 - 9/9/1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Equipment Memory 2/14/1978 - 6/22/1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Software 3/11/1974 - 7/26/1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Procurement Evaluation: Telecommunication Services 12/15/1978 - 5/25/1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Analysis 10/2/1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Analysis 6/16/1970 - 8/19/1980 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Analysis Studies 3/1/1974 - 3/7/1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Lease/Sale Analysis 6/11/1970 - 8/28/1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Third Party Leasing Companies 6/8/1971 - 3/15/1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Procurement, Lease/Purchase: Third Party Leasing Costs 1977 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Procurement, Maintenance: Emerson 12/14/1979 - 7/10/1980 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Procurement, Maintenance: DEC 5/7/1970 - 3/27/1973 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Procurement, Maintenance: IBM 1/23/1970 - 6/22/1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Procurement, Maintenance: General 8/18/1971 - 9/29/1977 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Procurement, Services: Plotting Services 3/19/1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Procurement, Services: Data Entry Services 12/15/1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Procurement, Systems: Pharmacy National Data Corporation 2/18/1981 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center - Pharmacy 5/23/1980 - 1/14/1982 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center ATD Admissions/ Transfer/Discharge System 1981 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center PAS Patient Accounting System 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Procurement, Software: Interlan Manuel Excerpt (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Procurement, Software: GC/CUE system description 9/20/1982 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Procurement, Software: GC/CUE 9/15/1982 - 11/15/1982 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Procurement, Software: IMSL 9/18/1973 - 10/15/1982 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Procurement, Software: Technicon Medical Information Systems Corporation 1982 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Procurement, Software: ASPEN Argonne National Laboratory 10/13/1982 - 10/20/1982 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, Candle Corporation 5/11/1981 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Procurement, Software: Argonne Code Center 6/12/1970 - 12/12/1979 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Procurement, Software: IBM CLCS 9/1/1981 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Procurement, Software: AUTOREF 4/18/1979 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Procurement, Software: BIBCARD 10/20/1976 - 11/12/1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Procurement, Software: Binary Software - Whitesmith Ltd. 3/15/1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, BMDP 1/24/1978 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, Brookings Institution 1/4/1979 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Procurement, Software: Cern, Word II 4/24/1981 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Procurement, Software: Computer Associates CASORT 5/9/1978 - 12/5/1978 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Procurement, Software: Comm-Pro 9/2/1978 - 8/7/1980 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Procurement, Software: DEC 6/10/1974 - 5/23/1980 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Procurement, Software: DYL-260 7/1974 - 1/29/1975 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Procurement, Software: Easy Reader 9/26/1975 - 10/15/1975 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, Cornell-Minidisk Manager 5/25/1979 - 2/8/1980 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, CS-COMP 3/23/1979 - 10/29/1979 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, CUNY 1/6/1978 - 11/3/1978 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Procurement, Software: Inpatient System 12/6/1977 - 1/31/1978 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Procurement, Software: License, IBM 1983 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, Intel System 2000 2/14/1983 - 6/9/1983 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Procurement, Software: INTEL-CMS Batch Monitor 10/31/1980 - 9/20/1982 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Procurement, Software: Letter Writing System 6/15/1981 - 6/19/1981 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Procurement, Software: Licenses, LISREL 10/1/1981 - 12/19/1982 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Procurement: Contracts 5/11/1982 - 11/5/1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Procurement, Systems: Datapoint OAIS (Operator Assistance Information System) 1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Procurement, Systems: Telecommunications OAIS 3/1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center PAS/AMI 11/26/1981 - 10/20/1982 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Procurement, Equipment: IBM 4/15/1970 - 5/4/1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center ATD 11/11/1981 - 9/21/1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Procurement, Systems Engineering Agreement: Analysis 1/12/1970 - 2/15/1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Procurement, Systems Engineering Agreement: General 9/8/1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Procurement, Systems Engineering Agreement: IBM 7/23/1970 - 11/6/1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Procurement, Systems: Medical Center 2/19/1980 - 12/7/1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Production Service 12/18/1979 - 8/31/1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Professional Organizations: ACM (Association for Computing Machinery) SIGUCC Newsletter 6/1972 - 5/1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Professional Organizations: CECC (California Educational Computing Consortium) 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)